Little misunderstanding, huh?
A little misunderstand...?
(Sheldon:)Galileo and the pope
had a little misunderstanding.
(Penny:)Anyway, I was talking
to Leonard this morning...
(Penny:)...and I think he feels really bad about it.
SHELDON:
Huh.
(Penny:)Well, how do you feel?
(Sheldon:)I don't understand the question.
(Penny:)Well, I'm just asking if it's difficult
to be fighting with your best friend.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I hadn't thought about it like that.
(Sheldon:)I wonder if I've been experiencing
physiological manifestations...
(Sheldon:)...of some sort
of unconscious emotional turmoil.
PENNY:
Wait, what?
(Sheldon:)I couldn't poop this morning.
(Penny:)You should just talk to him.
I'm sure you guys can work this out.
- It's certainly preferable to my plan.
- Which was?
(Sheldon:)A powerful laxative.
(Penny:)Okay, so you absolutely
should talk to him.
(Penny:)I know Leonard values you as a friend.
He told me without your little idea...